[
  {"question": "اكتب: قسطنطينية", "answer": "قسطنطينية"},
  {"question": "اكتب: إمبراطورية", "answer": "إمبراطورية"},
  {"question": "اكتب: هيدروكسيد", "answer": "هيدروكسيد"},
  {"question": "اكتب: مستشفى", "answer": "مستشفى"},
  {"question": "اكتب: جامعة", "answer": "جامعة"},
  {"question": "اكتب: هاتف", "answer": "هاتف"},
  {"question": "اكتب: سيارة", "answer": "سيارة"},
  {"question": "اكتب: مدرسة", "answer": "مدرسة"},
  {"question": "اكتب: مطار", "answer": "مطار"},
  {"question": "اكتب: نهر", "answer": "نهر"}
]
